

# DIEGO MUÑOZ BELTRÁN

# **CONTACT**

✓ Madrid, Spainin diegomunozbeltran

**೧/**₩ diegombeltran +34 676 640 409

www.diegomunozbeltran.com

yo@diegomunozbeltran.com

# **ABOUT ME**

I'm a 29 years old network engineering student in love with IT world. I spend most of my spare time looking for new amazing projects to discover. I enjoy managing bare metal servers at home, and I automate most of the things I develop, doing so in an agile way of thinking. When I'm not in front of the screen, I love watching movies, playing the electric guitar, boxing, chess and tango.

# **LANGUAGES**

Spanish Native
English C1 (TOEIC 960/990)

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **DEVOPS ENGINEER, BBVA NEXT TECHNOLOGIES**

Madrid, Spain — 2017-Present

#### Focused primarily on:

- Cloud: Amazon Web Services, GCE, Azure
- Infrastructure as Code: Ansible, Terraform
- CI/CD tools: GitLabCI, Jenkins
- Container Orchestration: Docker, Kubernetes, Openshift
- Agile Methodologies: Scrum, Kanban
- Distributed Architectures

# SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR, BIOMEDICAL IMAGING AND INSTRUMENTATION GROUP, HOSPITAL GENERAL GREGORIO MARAÑÓN

Madrid, Spain — 2013-2017

#### **Topics covered:**

- Virtualization: VMWare Vsphere, KVM
- Networking: Cisco devices, VLAN management
- Cybersecurity: Fortinet, pfSense
- Monitoring: Sensu, NagiOS, Zabbix, Grafana
- Scripting: *Python, Bash*

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER, FREELANCE

Madrid, Spain — 2013-2016

#### Some projects and technologies used:

- Asociación de Científicos Fundación Alicia Koplowitz website
  - https://www.asociaciondecientificos-fundak.org
- PSYSCAN website
  - http://www.psyscan.eu
- Tools and technologies: Drupal 7/8, Jekyll, Pelican, Ghost, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, PHP.

# **EDUCATION**

#### **TELEMATIC ENGINEERING DEGREE**

Escuela Técnica Superior de Ingeniería y Sistemas de Telecomunicación, Universidad Politécnica de Madrid — 2009

Part-time student

# **SOFT SKILLS**

Leadership
Proactive Attitude
Learning
Motivation



# **TAGS**

Linux, RHEL/CentOS/Fedora, Debian, FreeBSD, pfSense, FortiOS, Ansible, Fortinet, Terraform, Kubernetes, Openshift, Chef, Nginx, Apache, MongoDB, MySQL, MariaDB, PostgreSQL, Nagios, Grafana, Telegraf, DNS, DHCP, OpenVPN, IPSEC, iptables, AWS, EC2, S3, VMWare, Route53, ESXI, Virtualbox, Proxmox, KVM, Git, GitHub, GitLab, JIRA, Bash, Java Python, C++, EE, Matlab, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, BIND, Exim, Postfix, Drupal, Joomla, Wordpress, Typo3, Ghost, Jekyll, Pelican.

# **PREFERENCES**

Linux, free open source software, DevOps culture, cybersecurity, auditing, pentesting, networks, cloud, infrastructure as code, automation, agile methodologies, virtualization and containerization, IoT, domotics, privacy, medicaloriented IT, learning

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

#### **AWS CERTIFIED SOLUTIONS ARCHITECT - ASSOCIATE**

ID: 193PCVX2DN1QQTSZ Date Earned: Apr 09, 2018 Valid Through: Apr 10, 2021

# **COURSES**

#### **ARCHITECTING WITH AWS**

Global Knowledge, 2017

# VMWARE VSPHERE ICM: INSTALL, CONFIGURE AND MANAGE 5.5

JMG Virtual Consulting S.L, 2014

# CERTIFICATION COURSE LPI (LINUX PROFESSIONAL INSTITUTE)

CAS Training, S.L, 2013

# AN INTRODUCTION TO INTERACTIVE PROGRAMMING IN PYTHON

Rice University (Coursera), 2013

#### SYSTEMS CYBERSECURITY

Escola Tècnica Superior D´ Enginyeria, 2008

#### **CSS LAYOUT WITH HTML5**

Berkeley University, 2012